https://newengland.com/account/privacy-policy/

By The Numbers
Could You Live Here?
Privacy Policy
New England Network is committed to protecting and maintaining your privacy. We understand that it is a privilege for us to be trusted with your personal information. To get full access to our services, we ask you to give us information that we understand is very important to you. Therefore, we want you to know exactly what information is collected, why we collect it, how we protect it, and how you can access or change it.
This policy covers only the information collected on the NewEngland.com domain. Sites that link to or from our site are not covered by this policy. We encourage you to read the privacy policies of every site that you visit. To ensure your comfort with NewEngland.com, this policy is linked to every page where we ask for information on our site. To change or access your personally identifiable information (PII) please click the “SIGN IN” link at the top of any NewEngland.com page.
We are continuously improving our site. Whenever a new feature on our web site requires a change to this policy, we will post a clear notice on all the pages of our site where the privacy policy appears. The principle behind this policy and our business is to only collect information with your knowledge and consent.
The Information We Collect
This policy refers to all information collected on the NewEngland.com domain. On our site, there are pages where we ask you to enter information in order to receive specific services.
When you register we will collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name and email address.
We invite your online comments to the articles we post on NewEngland.com, and we reserve the right to remove any comment at the discretion of our editors.
How We Use This Information
When you first register with us on the NewEngland.com domain, we ask for your email address. Once you supply this information, you will be able to receive emails promoting content, important information about our site, about your subscription to our newsletter, or other offers or promotions. All information sent via email will come directly from NewEngland.com, and you may use the unsubscribe link in your email to remove your address from our list at any time. We will never sell or rent your information to anyone else. New England Network is owned and operated by Yankee Publishing, Inc., which is comprised of different operating groups. Any information we save about you may be shared among these operating groups. Occasionally you may receive offers from these operating groups. To remove your name from these lists, click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any communications.
All information on current and former members is retained in our database solely for customer service purposes.
Children’s Information
We do not knowingly collect or maintain information at our website from children under the age of 13, and no part of our website is structured to attract those under 13.
Cookies
The NewEngland.com domain uses cookies every time you visit our site. Cookies are used to remember information you have already entered, for instance your password, so that you will not have to re-enter them every time you visit. We never use cookies to collect additional personally identifiable information about you. You can ask your browser to not accept cookies or to notify you when a cookie is being sent if you do not wish to accept cookies. You can also manually delete all cookie files from your computer. We use them only to make your visit to our site more enjoyable.
IP Addresses
The NewEngland.com domain uses IP addresses to analyze trends, administer the site, track users’ movements inside the site, determine which site referred users to us, and gather very general demographic information. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.
What You Should Know Concerning The Future
New England Network is committed to your privacy. However, if another company ever acquires New England Network, all of our assets, including information we’ve gathered, become the property of the new owner. If this happens, the new owner’s policies may override this Privacy Policy. Also, if New England Network ever goes out of business, all its assets, including the information we have gathered, may be sold or dissolved.
Yankee Magazine Subscriptions and Online Store Purchases
If you subscribe to Yankee Magazine via print, web, or mobile device; or make a purchase in our online store, our customer service provider Palm Coast Data, LLC will collect personally identifiable information from you that may include your name, email address, billing address, shipping address, phone number and credit-card information.  Yankee Magazine on occasion shares its mailing list with approved advertisers to promote products or services we think our readers will enjoy.  If you do not wish to receive these offers, please Contact Us.
Questions, Comments?
If you ever have any questions or comments, please contact us.
Yankee Publishing, Inc., publishers of Yankee Magazine, NewEngland.com, The Old Farmer’s Almanac and Almanac.com
Topics TravelTravelConnecticutConnecticutHartfordLitchfield HillsMysticNew HavenNew LondonMaineMaineBangorBar HarborBoothbayCamdenKennebunkportOgunquitPortlandYorkMassachusettsMassachusettsBerkshiresBostonCape CodConcordMartha's VineyardNantucketProvincetownSalemSpringfieldNew EnglandNew EnglandBeachesFestivals & FairsLakesMountainsPlaces to EatPlaces to StayRoad TripsThings to DoVacationsNew HampshireNew HampshireLakes RegionPortsmouthSeacoastWhite MountainsRhode IslandRhode IslandBlock IslandBristolNarragansettNewportPawtucketProvidenceWesterlyWickfordVermontVermontBenningtonBrattleboroBurlingtonManchesterMontpelierStoweWoodstockFoodFoodAppetizersAppetizersCheeseDips & SpreadsSeafood AppetizersSnacksBeveragesBreadsBreadsBiscuits & RollsQuick BreadsBreakfast & BrunchBreakfast & BrunchBreakfastBreakfast CasserolesCoffee CakesDonutsEggsMuffinsPancakesCondimentsCondimentsJams & SpreadsMaple SyrupSaucesCooking AdviceCooking AdviceCookbooksKitchen TipsStep by Step RecipesDessertsDessertsCakes & FrostingsCandyCookies & BarsCrisps, Crumbles & CobblersCupcakesFrozen DessertsFruit RecipesPies & PastriesPuddings & CustardsWhoopie PiesLunchLunchLobster RollsQuicheSandwichesMain DishesMain DishesBoiled DinnerCasserolesClambakesFish & SeafoodLobsterMeatMeat PiesMeatlessNew England FoodPastaPizzaPot RoastPoultrySlow CookingNew England MadeSaladsSaladsDeli SaladsFruit SaladsGreen SaladsSeasonal RecipesSide DishesSide DishesBaked BeansPickles & PreservesPotatoesRice & GrainsVegetablesSoups, Stews, & ChowdersSoups, Stews, & ChowdersChowdersSoupsStewsSpecial OccasionsSpecial OccasionsBarbecueChristmasChurch SuppersEasterHalloweenIndependence DayPassoverPotluckSt. Patricks DayThanksgivingValentine’s DayLivingLivingBackyardCleaningCraftsGardeningHome DecorHome RemediesHome Repair & DIYHomesHumorMade in New EnglandNew England EnvironmentNew England HistoryNew England NostalgiaPestsProfilesTrivia
Free Guides
Yankee Magazine’s Ultimate New England Winter Guide
Yankee Magazine’s Ultimate Holiday Guide
Best New England Vacations: Things to Do in Boston, Maine Vacations, Things to Do in New Hampshire, Things to Do in Rhode Island and More
Yankee Magazine’s Ultimate New England Summer Guide
63 Reasons Why We Love the Cape & Islands
Yankee Magazine’s Ultimate Guide to Autumn in New England
Best of New England in the Fall: Fall Foliage, Great Hikes, Apple Picking and More!
Best of New England Fall Travel: Best Places to See Foliage in New England, Best Fall Drives in New England, Things To Do In Maine, Things To Do in the Berkshires, Things To Do in Vermont, and More!
Best Apple Recipes: Easy Desserts with Apples, Best Apples for Apple Pie, Our Favorite Apple Turnover Recipe, and More!
Best of New England Seafood Recipes: How to Cook Scallops, How to Make Clam Chowder, Cooking Lobster Tails, Cod Fillet Recipes, Haddock Recipes and More.
Lost and Vintage Recipes: Breakfasts and Breads from the Editors of Yankee Magazine
Lost and Vintage Recipes: Desserts and Sweets from the Editors of Yankee Magazine
Remember MeThis setting should only be used on your home or work computer.
Lost your password? Create New Password
No password? Sign up
×
